Hi,
okay, so I just really quickly wanted to show you,
my feedback, because So I think overall, I just really want to simplify this,
like, a ton. I think, as a girly-pop who works with AI all the
time, this is currently looking, like, extremely AI-coded,
which means they love AI tools,
love to just add unnecessary information,
and, like, things that look like buttons that aren't buttons,
and then, like, repeated the same information over and over again.
So, I think we just, like, the,
the stuff is here, now we just, like,
kill stuff. two more overall things,
I think some of the text needs to be bigger,
cause the people that are looking at this site are probably much older,
and they're not gonna read the little, the little notes.
and then, orange is not part of the branding,
so let's just make sure that we're using the brand colors throughout,
which is the off-white, the green,
I think there's two greens, but there's a darker green for sure,
and the red as, like, the accent color.
and then, white and black is fine, but I'd rather go off-white than just
white, everywhere. Cool,
and then, also, like, just making sure the text fonts are
within the branding as well.
then here, let's kill the Simi Hills Golf Course,
18th Hole Fairway Dining, let's kill Breakfast through Dinner,
70's a Week, this little,
emble-ish emblem, and then this thing,
this four thing, which is, like, unnecessary information.
let's kill this whole thing,
these three, let's kill Life on the 18th hole see me see me how's
like this can just be right under American Classics,
Texas Patients, then we have the menu, but you don't really know that
you're looking at the menu,
so I think, like, the name menu needs to be somewhere here because there's
just so much information that you're looking at,
like, you don't really know what you're looking at. Let's kill these.
Button things, Live Music, this is great,
thank you so much. If there's any way we can add images to
these, that would be great, if not,
no worries. Full Service and Drop-off Kit, let's just kill this,
this whole thing. the Instagram is great.
I just, it needs to look like the actual Instagram,
I think these images are not from the Instagram,
and it's just like repeated, there's like four of the same salads.
This image is not, I don't see it on the Instagram,
this is repeated. This is blurry.
This is blurry. so, it would be great to just show the actual Instagram.
And then, Again,
like, just, information is repeated, we already have this button above,
we don't need this information. We don't need this information,
let's just kill it all. And no more orange. And then this is repeated
right here. So, just kill that first part.
Cool. Menu. Menu's great.
The clickable part is awesome. These are awesome.
I think one big thing, here's an example, not this one. Here's an example,
like, they have, you can look at each
of their, their menus here,
and then you see the PDF,
which we have, and is in the original,
website, so I would love to have a button where you can click to
view the PDF, or like, see whole menu here,
so then someone can just have the whole menu on their phone as well,
instead of it being like, super interactive,
as it is currently. Cool,
that's the menu, catering.
I think this is,
this is fine. Let's just make sure,
like, all this information is absolutely correct.
I don't, didn't know we had these catering packages,
so if we do, amazing. If not,
let's just update them with the correct packages.
and then, these pictures aren't really pictures.
These are of catering, so I don't really want to,
like, show something that it's not.
if we have pictures of catering, great. If not,
I think we can just do,
show nothing. No images would be great.
I don't think, we don't need this whole section. Thank for your cool
events. this is great. If we can have images in here from the bands,
that would be great. This about section is fine.
I think. Let's just, like, keep this as fine.
This, it's, please remove these.
This, like, rounded, and then with,
with a, with a title on the image is just,
like, not great to look at,
and it's, AI loves to do that. I don't know,
this is not true. So,
let's just make sure that this, let's just grab the about section from
the current site. this is, let's remove this, let's just remove this whole thing.
Because we already have a catering. And,
same with the Instagram note here. Like,
these images are definitely not the images that we want to show.
Thank you. Bye-bye. Let's make sure the images are the,
what is on the Instagram. who's here?
I think that could, that could move up. and let's use images of Mark
and Marco. And if we don't have images of them,
let's not have images of random things.
So, no images at all. this,
let's remove that. And remove this,
we already have the Instagram up here.
Remove this whole thing. Cool,
and then contacts. is, this is fine,
so let's just triple check that this is actually correct.
And then all of these, like, these, these outlines look different,
like for some reason the stroke on the musicians and bands is different.
It's thicker than the stroke on the holiday and special closures and music,
and then live music on the patio and opening hours have a title,
but musicians and bands and holiday and special closures do not,
so, like, all of this is just, like,
the design is just not consistent,
so if we can just simplify and show consistent design,
that would be great. I'll see we don't need this send a message,
we do not need this follow us, we don't need this,
we don't need this. cool. Great.
And then, I just wanted to, and then can you,
can we make it so you can click on the homepage here,
with the grill on the green logo. Cool.
So, again, wanna just make it, like,
super, super simple. here's some other examples,
like Wood Ranch, you just literally have the logo up top,
gorgeous video of food, then order online,
reserve, menu, locations, catering and events,
gift cards. And then just,
like, three little things into pictures,
that's it. And then the Instagram,
yeah, that's it. So, that's great.
Here's another example, literally theirs is just an image of gorgeous food,
and then the bottom, which is great.
this person's too. Has, like, big images,
and then they're catering in events, which is, I'm not saying this is,
okay, this is way too much information. yeah. Okay.
Cool. Thank you so much. I really appreciate,
all of this. And then, one more thing is, the,
when you send the, the website.
Can we just be sure that there's a social icon,
and that the icon is an image of our absolute best food
image. I've taken, I took a lot of food imagery,
and I know you guys have too, so I would just love to,
like, see that footage,
and also pictures of the course,
which I've also taken, throughout the website.
Because that's, like, the best part about the restaurant.
So, yeah. Thank you so much.